(Howard:)So listen, guys,
the reason he was up late...
(Howard:)...is because he was taking care
of Amy.
(Howard:)- She's kind of upset.
- Why?
(Leonard:)Her feelings got hurt because
you went dress shopping without her.
(Bernadette:)I told you that would happen.
(Penny:)This is her first time being a bridesmaid,
and she's getting a Iittle crazy with it.
(Bernadette:)She keeps on telling us stories about
bridesmaid traditions in other cuItures...
(Bernadette:)...and they're all about getting naked
and washing each other.
(Penny:)She keeps trying to figure out
if our cycles have synced up...
(Penny:)...so we can call ourselves
"The Three Menstra-teers."
(Bernadette:)We thought it would be easier
to look at dresses one time without her.
(Bernadette:)- I feel terrible.
- I know, me too. We'll talk to her.
(Penny:)Hey, wait, how did she find out?
Raj did it. Ugh.
(Howard:)And he says he would do it again.